question_data =[
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
         "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
         "question": "Bill Cipher in the show &quot;Gravity Falls&quot; is the good guy.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                          "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
                                          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "Thomas Crapper was a plumber who invented the flushing toilet.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                          "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
         "question": "The &quot;Pepe&quot; meme originated from a comic drawn by Matt Furie called &quot;Boy&#039;s Club&quot;?",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                          "question": "Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members",
                                          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
    ]

